Hartel, Lois Photographs 6247 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Lois Hartel Photographs
1978-2004
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Hartel, Lois
6247 P
1.5 cubic feet
1.5 linear ft.
Photographs.
6191401
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, April 02, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 25, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5780: ILGWU records 6247: Lois Hartel Papers
Hartel, Lois
6191401
- Lois Hartel "The Joseph A. Beirne - Community Service Award" (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  17 photographs
- 1991 Beirne Award, Inner Harbor, Baltimore (Box 1, Folder 2)
  35 photographs; negatives
- ILGWU - 37th Convention 1980 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  6 photographs
- Lois Hartel - Misc. Photos (1) (Box 1, Folder 4)
  26 photographs
- Lois Hartel - Misc. Photos. (2) (Box 1, Folder 5)
  30 photographs
- Misc. Photos (Box 1, Folder 6)
  9 photographs
- "Every Vote Counts' group photo (Box 1, Folder 7)
  1 photograph
- 'Professional Hints for the Host and Hostess' booklet (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Lois Hartel - Clinton - Gore - 1996 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  22 photographs
- Lois Hartel Photos - no date (Box 1, Folder 10)
  14 photographs
- Misc. Photos (Box 1, Folder 11)
  7 photographs
- Photos from Lois Hartel - 3/2003 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- The Immigrant Workers Freedom Ride - booklet (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Miscellaneous (Box 1, Folder 14)
- United for Justice (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Stand up for your rights organize! (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Miscellaneous (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Aladdin Unfair - protest (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Frontier (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Miscellaneous (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Murphy Brown Party - Fall 1992 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Senator Musto, ILGWU (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Bill Gable at the piano (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Local 295 Retirees 10th Anniv. 1987 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  2 photographs
- Ribbon cutting at ILGWU Democratic Headquarters (Box 1, Folder 25)
- ILGWU for Casey and Kline (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Miscellaneous (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Lois Hartel - 10/1990 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- 1989 ILGWU Convention (Box 1, Folder 29)
- ILGWU - Hazelton- (Box 1, Folder 30)
- June 1992 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Stop Sweatshops - Washington, D.C. - 1998 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Miscellaneous (Box 1, Folder 33)
  5 photographs
- Local 166 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- June 1978 - Washington, D.C. - Legislative Conference (Box 1, Folder 35)
  3 photographs
- 1980 Convention (Box 1, Folder 36)
  13 photographs
- Solidarity Day 1981 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Carribean Delegation visit 1981 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  18 photographs
- Carribean Delegation 1981 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  33 photographs
- Pittston - X-mas Party -- 1982 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  10 photographs
- Rank & File Institute -- 1982 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  20 photographs
- Christmas Party -- 1983 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  15 photographs
- Convention -- 1983 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  16 photographs
- Mondale visit - Leslie Fay -- 1983 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Wyoming Valley Dist. Council Mtg. -- 1983 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- 1984 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  news clips
- ACTWU - Import Rally - Scranton -- 1984 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Ann Daley & Helen DePhillips - Retirement -- 1984 (May) (Box 2, Folder 9)
- 1st Pittston Tomato Festival -- 1984 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  11 photographs
- Allentown Conference & Meeting -- 1985 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- ILG Cacus Dinner - Phila. -- 1985 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Pittston Dist. Christmas -- 1985 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Tomato Festival (1) -- 1985 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Tomato Festival (2) -- 1985 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- CLUW Convention -- 1986 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Convention -- 1986 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Lady Coral -- 1986 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  19 photographs
- Nom. Mtg. -- 1986 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Dist. Council Elections -- 1986 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- E. Board Convention -- 1986 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Import Demo - 7/1986 -- Pittston -- 1986 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Import Demo - Washington -- 1986 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- 1989 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- 1989 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- District Council - Sam & Evelyns Last Meeting -- 1988 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Dress & Spts. Contract Meeting -- 1988 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- PA -- AFL-CIO Q's Comm. Awards -- 1988 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Unity -- 1988 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  23 photographs
- 1989 (1) (Box 2, Folder 30)
- 1989 (2) (Box 2, Folder 31)
  24 photographs
- 1989 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  25 photographs
- 1989 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  21 photographs
- Conference (Oct.) -- 1989 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- 1990 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- W-B Chorus Convention -- 1992 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  12 photographs
- Leslie Fay -- 1994 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Lois Cartel - cards -- 1995 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Photo album photos -- 1999 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- 1999 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  28 photographs
- Chorus - WUIA -- TV -- 1999 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Chorus -- 1999 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Unidentified Loose Items (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Members -- Retirees -- Harrisburg (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Unidentified Photos (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Unidentified Photos (Box 3, Folder 10)
- 2004 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  news clippings
- Unidentified Photos (Box 3, Folder 12)
  31 photographs
- April 10th - Import Rally (1) (Box 3, Folder 13)
- April 10th Import Rally (2) (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Retirees - X-Mas Party & Must save for paper (Box 3, Folder 15)